{
  "isTheory": true,
  "openingRemarks": "Find the solution to the following equations",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(6d + 8 = 14 + 3d \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6d + 8 &= 14 + 3d \\\\\n6d - 3d &= 14 - 8  \\\\\n3d  &= 6  \\\\\n\\dfrac{3d}{3} &= \\dfrac{6}{3} \\\\\nd &= 2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6d + 8\\) if \\(d=2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6d + 8 &= 6(2) + 8 \\\\\n&= 12 + 8  \\\\\n&= 20\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(14 + 3d\\) if \\(d=2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n14 + 3d &= 14 + 3(2) \\\\\n&= 14 + 6  \\\\\n&= 20\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2(h + 1) = 5h - 7 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(h + 1) &= 5h - 7 \\\\\n2h + 2 &= 5h - 7  \\\\\n2 + 7  &= 5h - 2h  \\\\\n9 &= 3h \\\\\n\\dfrac{9}{3} &= \\dfrac{3h}{3} \\\\\n3 &= h \\\\\nh &= 3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(h + 1)\\) if \\(h=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(h + 1) &= 2(3 + 1) \\\\\n &=  2(4)  \\\\\n&= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5h - 7\\) if \\(h=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5h - 7 &= 5(3) - 7 \\\\\n &= 15 - 7  \\\\\n&= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(n - 12 = 32 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nn - 12 &= 32 \\\\\nn &= 32 + 12  \\\\\nn &= 44 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 32</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(n - 12\\) if \\(n=44\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nn - 12 &= 44 - 12 \\\\\n&= 32\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(y + 16 = -9 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\ny + 16 &= -9 \\\\\ny &= -9 - 16  \\\\\ny &= -25 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -9</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(y + 16\\) if \\(y=-25\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\ny + 16 &= -25 + 16 \\\\\n&= -9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(f + \\dfrac{2}{3} = 4 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nf + \\dfrac{2}{3} &= 4 \\\\\n3 \\times f + 3 \\times \\dfrac{2}{3} &= 3 \\times 4  \\\\\n3f + 2 &= 12 \\\\\n3f &= 12 - 2 \\\\\n3f &= 10 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3f}{3} &= \\dfrac{10}{3} \\\\\nf &= \\dfrac{10}{3}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 4</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(f + \\dfrac{2}{3}\\) if \\(f=\\frac{10}{3}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nf + \\dfrac{2}{3} &= \\dfrac{10}{3} + \\dfrac{2}{3} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{12}{3} \\\\\n&= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(d - 3.9 = 8.2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nd - 3.9 &= 8.2 \\\\\nd &= 8.2 + 3.9 \\\\\nd &= 12.1 \n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 8.2</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(d - 3.9\\) if \\(d=12.1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nd - 3.9 &= 12.1 - 3.9 \\\\\n&= 8.2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7x + 10 - 6x + 3 = 5 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n7x + 10 - 6x + 3 &= 5 \\\\\n7x - 6x &= 5 - 10 - 3 \\\\\nx &= -8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 5</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(7x + 10 - 6x + 3\\) if \\(x=-8\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n7x + 10 - 6x + 3 &= 7(-8) + 10 - 6(-8) + 3 \\\\\n&= -56 + 10 + 48 + 3 \\\\\n&= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6(n - 1) - 5n = -14 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6(n - 1) - 5n &= -14 \\\\\n6n - 6 - 5n &= -14 \\\\\n6n - 5n &= -14 + 6 \\\\\nn &= -8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -14</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6(n - 1) - 5n\\) if \\(n=-8\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6(n - 1) - 5n &= 6(-8 - 1) - 5(-8) \\\\\n&= 6(-9) + 40 \\\\\n&= -54 + 40 \\\\\n&= -14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8(3p + 5) - 23(p - 1) = 35 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8(3p + 5) - 23(p - 1) &= 35 \\\\\n24p + 40 - 23p + 23  &= 35 \\\\\n24p - 23p &= 35 - 40 - 23 \\\\\np &= -28\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 35</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8(3p + 5) - 23(p - 1)\\) if \\(p=-28\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8(3p + 5) - 23(p - 1) &= 8(3(-28) + 5) - 23(-28 - 1) \\\\\n&= 8(-84 + 5) - 23(-29) \\\\\n&= 8(-79) + 667 \\\\\n&= -632 + 667 \\\\\n&= 35\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-18m = -72 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-18m &= -72 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-18m}{-18} &= \\dfrac{-72}{-18} \\\\\nm &= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -72</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-18m\\) if \\(m=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-18m &= -18(4) \\\\\n&= 72\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n"
    }
  ]
}
